travelinsuranceagencies.net 2015-12-26

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy governs your use of the travelinsuranceagencies.net website (“Site”) operated by BBO Partners Co., LTD. We regard your privacy seriously and provide this Privacy Policy to describe which information we collect, how we collect it, how we use it and the circumstances under which we may share it.

Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

You may use the Site without registering. You may also register and voluntarily provide personally identifiable information (“PII”), such as your name and email address. When you create your account, we will ask you to create a username and password. You will be able to enter PII into your password-protected account. You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and your account information. In addition, 9Rank.com allows you to set up profiles that may be viewed by users of the Site. To enrich your experience, you may choose to include some PII in your public profile so that other users can identify you. You can change or delete your profile at anytime.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) such as your internet protocol address and information associated with your computer, browser and network to deliver services or information, provide notices, track usage, verify your authority to use the Site, store your preferences, and generally improve the content and functionality of the Site.

Cookies

We may use small text files stored in your browser called cookies to store your preferences, record session information, and improve your experience on the Site as described in the previous sentence.

Language

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp .

Advertising

We will not share your PII with advertising companies. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads. Such advertising companies may set cookies and collect session information, such as your IP address, to target advertisements to you based on your internet protocol address, and information associated with your computer, browser or network. You may be able to configure your browser to reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

Disclosure

We will not intentionally disclose PII in your account except as specifically described in this Privacy Policy. Non-PII may be shared with third parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements. We may also disclose your PII and Non-PII if we believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority, or to prevent harm to yourself or others. In addition, we may transfer your PII to a successor entity upon a change of control of travelinsuranceagencies.net, sale, merger, or other corporate reorganization. Such successor entity will be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

Email

Email addresses are used for identification, inviting new friends to travelinsuranceagencies.net, searching for and finding friends, for general communication, and to send notifications to you. To facilitate searching for and finding friends on the Site, travelinsuranceagencies.net allows users to search for other members using text searches, first and last name, email address, and other attributes. Users can invite friends to join tinmoi.vn by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. travelinsuranceagencies.net stores these email addresses so that the respondents may be added to the friend’s list of the member sending the invitations, and also to establish relationships between users. travelinsuranceagencies.net does not sell invitation email addresses or use them for any other purpose.

Links to Third Party Websites

The Site contains links to other websites. Your use of websites to which the Site link is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on such third party websites.

Security

travelinsuranceagencies.net employs procedural and technological measures, such as password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to protect your information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

Policy Changes

travelinsuranceagencies.net reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, and will post any revisions on the Site. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Site will be subject to the then-current Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last revised February 8, 2011.

Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

If you have questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us, email: ntlong090@gmail.com?
